<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.microsoft.Teams</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
    <name>Microsoft Teams</name>
    <summary>Microsoft Teams for Linux is your chat-centered workspace in Office 365</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">O Microsoft Teams é o hub de trabalho em equipe do Office 365</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Microsoft Teams es el concentrador de trabajo en equipo de Office 365</summary>
    <description>
        <p>
            All your team conversations, files, meetings, and apps live together in a single shared workspace. This app requires a paid Office 365 commercial subscription, or a free or trial subscription of Microsoft Teams. If you’re not sure about your company’s subscription or the services you have access to, visit Office.com/Teams to learn more or contact your IT department.
        </p>

        <p>
            NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by Microsoft Corporation.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR">
        <p>
            O Teams reúne tudo em um espaço de trabalho compartilhado com o qual você pode trabalhar em praticamente qualquer lugar, facilitando a conversa com a equipe, a colaboração em arquivos e o trabalho com os aplicativos favoritos. O Teams reúne tudo em um espaço de trabalho compartilhado com o qual você pode trabalhar em praticamente qualquer lugar, facilitando a conversa com a equipe, a colaboração em arquivos e o trabalho com os aplicativos favoritos.
        </p>
        <p>
            NOTA: Este aplicativo não foi empacotado pelo Microsoft Corporation
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="es">
        <p>
            Teams lo reúne todo en un área de trabajo compartida, lo que te permite trabajar desde cualquier lugar y facilita que tu equipo chatee, colabore en archivos y trabaje con sus aplicaciones favoritas. Esta aplicación requiere una suscripción comercial de Office 365 de pago o una suscripción gratuita o de prueba de Microsoft Teams.
        </p>
        <p>NOTA: Esta aplicación no ha sido empaquetado por Microsoft Corporation
        </p>
    </description>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.microsoft.Teams.desktop</launchable>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Microsoft Teams</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/Microsoft-Teams-1000x563.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Move conversations from email into Microsoft Teams with rich formatting, including attachments</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/58c77173c6d8a-58c77173c821dMove-conversations-from-email-into-Microsoft-Teams-with-rich-formatting-including-attachments..png-1000x666.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Ad hoc and scheduled voice and video meetings right from within Microsoft Teams</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/Ad-hoc-and-scheduled-voice-and-video-meetings-right-from-within-Microsoft-Teams-1000x563.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>New bots help you complete tasks within your conversations</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/New-bots-help-you-complete-tasks-within-your-conversations.-1000x666.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <developer_name>Microsoft Corporation</developer_name>
    <url type="homepage">https://teams.microsoft.com/downloads</url>

    <releases>
        <release version="1.3.00.25560" date="2020-10-05"/>
        <release version="1.3.00.16851" date="2020-06-29"/>
        <release version="1.3.00.5153" date="2020-03-20"/>
        <release version="1.3.00.958" date="2020-01-20"/>
        <release date="2019-12-04" version="1.2.00.32451"/>
    </releases>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-info">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
</component>
